مالك مش باين ليه
what's the matter why have you Faded so?
قلبك تايه من مدة كبيرة
Your heart had been astray away for oh so long
خايف تتكلم ليه
Why are you so afraid to talk?
في عيونك حيرة وحكاوي كتيرة
In your eyes bewilderment hides and oh so many tales
متغير ياما عن زمان
You've changed so much from before
قافل على قلبك البيبان
You've shut your heart off every door
حبيت وفارقت كام مكان
You've loved and parted so many places
عايش جواك
that dwell within you
إحساسك كل يوم يقل
Each day you feel a little less
وتخطي وخطوتك تذل
You try and tread but with each footstep demeaned
من كتر ما أحبطوك تمل
From how they've humiliated you, you tire
فين تلق دواك
But where do you find solace ?
بتودع حلم كل يوم
Everyday, you bid farewell to another dream
تستفرد بيك الهموم
The anguish plagues you all around
وكله كوم والغربة كوم والجرح كبير
But nothing beats homesickness
مبتديش حاجة اهتمام
You don't pay anything any mind
أهلا أهلا سلام سلام
Hello ... Hello .. Goodbye ... Goodbye
بقا طبعك قلة الكلام ومفيش تفسير
Silence has overtaken your temperament for no reason
داري داري يا قلبي مهما تداري
Shield ... shield Oh my poor heart, how you can shield
قصاد الناس حزننا مكشوف
your pain is still plain for the world to see
وأهو عادي عادي
But it is normal Normal
محدش في الدنيا دي بيتعلق بشي
That you cannot be attached in this world to anything..
إلا وفراقه يشوف
Except a parting is due
كل اللي معاك في الصورة غاب
Everyone with you in your photographs is now absent
وطنك والأهل والصحاب
Your homeland, your family and friends
كم واحد ودع وساب من غير أسباب
How many bid farewell to part with no reason
شايف في عينيك نظرة حنين
I can see a look of longing in your eyes
بتحن لمين ولا مين
How many can you long for?
طول عمرها ماشية السنين
The years have always been on the move
والناس ركاب
And people are but mere passengers
مع دقة عقرب الساعات
With every tick tock of the clock